So, hello everyone, in the previous video, I have made something like in the export const
logout function.
You have to add this line of code, like console.log error in the logout and you also have
to pass this response as status code, okay.
So, add these two lines of code and now in this video we are going to work with this update
profile controller, okay.
So, but for this we are going to use some service which is known as Cloudinary, but also
before that you need to pass the data, okay.
So you need to use one metadata which is called as the cookie parser.
So in the app.js what do you do?
Just go there and import cookie parser from cookie parser, okay.
So import cookie parser from cookie parser and now what we are going to do is we are going to
just use this middleware, so app.use cookie parser, all right.
Make sure to add these two lines of code because we need to parse the data which is coming
from the back and side, okay.
So control s and now we are going to just go to the, go to this Cloudinary website.
So I will just go and let you know, okay.
Okay, so let's go to the Cloudinary website, Cloudinary, so we are going to sign up, sign up
for free.
I am going to use my account, so you should also use your account, okay.
It is, so as you can see this is the interface, so what you are going to do is like you
are going to copy this cloud name and now in the dot en we file you are going to just store
this one, okay, so you can store this like cloud slash key, cloudinary key, cloudinary
underscore key equals to this one, control save and now we need to go to the setting section,
so as we can see that here and now you can go to this API like this setting here as you
can see and if you can key is, sorry, if you can go to this setting and there will be
API keys, so I have already created an active API key, so I can copy that one, so I can
take this and just copy that and paste it inside of the dot en we, okay.
So we can name this as key or whatever, I will just rename it after a few moments but for
the time being I am just going to store this as control, as and control we, so after this
one, so it would be better if we just name all of these three values as something better,
okay, so how about this one, so wait, cloudinary underscore cloud underscore name equals
to and let's go here and now we are going to just copy this one, okay, so where was the
cloud name, wait a second, so cloud name, so I am going to copy this and paste this,
control as and now for API key, so cloudinary, cloudinary underscore API underscore key equals
to and now let's go back to this setting section, okay, so settings, so now we have
this default API key, okay, so API key, the cloudinary API key control plus V and for the
secret key, also we are going to name one, so cloudinary, cloudinary secret underscore
key equals to control, I think both are same how, one second, that's API key and that's
API secret key should be same only, okay, okay, that requires a confirmation code, okay,
let's approve this one, okay, I have made this one, okay, right, so now let's copy this
API key, okay, so API key, let's paste like this and the second thing is here, you can
copy this one and secret key can be pasted here, control as, now again go back and we have
this, yeah, control as safe, so now we have successfully set up this one, so in the next
video I'm going to tell you how to configure all the like routes in the cloudinary.